<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech &amp; Thought by Yash</title>
    <link>https://yashreddy1963.github.io/Blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tech &amp; Thought by Yash</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:28:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yashreddy1963.github.io/Blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IndiaFOSS 2024</title>
      <link>https://yashreddy1963.github.io/Blogs/posts/indiafoss-2k24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yashreddy1963.github.io/Blogs/posts/indiafoss-2k24/</guid>
      <description>So finally I attended and volunteered at IndiaFOSS conference Journey In April 2023, Mangesh, Jacob, and I attended the PuneFOSS conference. Inspired by this event, we decided to organize something similar in Solapur. Our first event took place in August 2023, followed by a meetup in March 2024. During this time, I was also volunteering with FOSS United Bangalore as a video editor, where I created intro promos for the BangaloreFOSS YouTube channel and edited speaker sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://yashreddy1963.github.io/Blogs/posts/fosshack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:30:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yashreddy1963.github.io/Blogs/posts/fosshack/</guid>
      <description>Attending My First Hackathon: FOSS Hack 2024 in Bangalore. Recently, I attended my first hackathon, “FOSSHack,” in Bangalore. My two friends and I decided to participate in this hackathon about 2–3 months ago, but we hadn’t decided what we were going to build. When only one month remained until the hackathon, we finally decided to make an app for Linux that would provide backgrounds for images or screenshots, either gradient or solid colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizing first tech meetup</title>
      <link>https://yashreddy1963.github.io/Blogs/posts/solapurfoss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 23:30:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yashreddy1963.github.io/Blogs/posts/solapurfoss/</guid>
      <description>Organizing my first tech FOSS Meetup This is my first general blog in which I will be sharing my experience organizing the first meet-up of SolapurFOSS. After the SolapurFOSS Conference SolapurFOSS is actually handled by my friend Mangesh, and under his lead, we conducted our first FOSS conference in Solapur on 27th August 2023. Later, after successfully organizing the SolapurFOSS conference, the three of us ( Me, Mangesh, and Jacob ) were deciding on conducting a Linux installation workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
